Inventory of the Gerald Fried papers, 1941-2014
University of Wyoming. American Heritage Center.
- Series III. Project Files
  - Sub-series 5. Movies
    - Cast a Long Shadow
      - Cinematic Photographs, Color, 1959 (Box 106)
      - Poster, 1959 (Box 106)
    - Cold Wind and August
      - CD and Reel-to-Reel, 1961 (Box 102 and Digital, ahcdm_02883_130)
      - Posters, 1961 (Box 106)
      - Score, undated (Box 27)
    - The Cry Baby Killer
      - CDs: Master, 1958 (Digital, ahcdm_02883_326-327)
      - Promotional Cinematic Photographs, Black & White and Color, 1958 (Box 105)
    - The Curse of Dracula
      - Cassette: Screen Archives - Gerald Fried, October 11, 1994 (Box 103)
      - Score, 1 of 2, undated (Box 27)
      - Score, 2 of 2, undated (Box 27)
      - Score, 1 of 2, undated (Box 27)
      - Score, 2 of 2, undated (Box 27)
    - Curse of the Faceless Man
      - Cinematic Photographs, Black & White, Color, 1958 (Box 106)
    - Death Watch
      - Cassette, 1966 (Box 100)
      - CDs: Master, 1966 (Digital, ahcdm_02883_238-239)
    - The Flame Barrier
      - CDs, 1958 (Digital, ahcdm_02883_320 and 340)
      - Cinematic Photograph, Color, 1958 (Box 106)
      - Score, 1 of 2, undated (Box 28)
      - Score, 2 of 2, undated (Box 28)
    - The Great Rights
      - Score, undated (Box 28)
    - The Grissom Gang
      - Cassette, 1971 (Box 100)
      - CDs and 4 Reel-to-Reels: 5-6, 29-30, Scenes 2501-2545 - Master, Sequenced, 1971 (Box 103 and Digital, ahcdm_02883_174, 207-210, 309)
      - Score, 1 of 2, 1970-1971 (Box 28)
      - Score, 2 of 2, 1970-1971 (Box 28)
    - High School Big Shot
      - Cinematic Photograph, Color, 1959 (Box 106)
    - I Bury the Living aka Killer on the Wall
      - Cinematic Photograph, Color, 1958 (Box 106)
      - Score, 1 of 2, undated (Box 29)
      - Score, 2 of 2, undated (Box 29)
    - I, Mobster
      - CDs, 1958 (Digital, ahcdm_02883_450)
      - Cinematic Photographs, Black & White, undated (Box 106)
      - Posters, 1956 (Box 106)
      - Score, undated (Box 30)
    - The Killing of Sister George
      - Cassette: Song, 1968 (Box 100)
      - Score and Correspondence, 1 of 2, 1968 (Box 31)
      - Score, 2 of 2, 1968 (Box 34)
    - The Legacy of L.S.B. Leakey
      - 2 Reel-to-Reels and CDs: WQED, Sequenced Master, undated (Box 103 and Digital, ahcdm_02883_223-226)
      - Score, undated (Box 32)
    - The Lost Missile
      - CDs, 1958 (Digital, ahcdm_02883_328-330)
      - Cinematic Photograph, Color, 1958 (Box 106)
      - Score, undated (Box 32)
    - Machine-Gun Kelly
      - Cassette: Screen Archives - Gerald Fried "Machine Gun Kelly" Demo Tape #3, October 19, 1994 (Box 103)
      - CDs:Demo #3, Unidentified, G. Fried Various X-fer 5-8-9-10-18, "Weed Work", Supplement, 1958 (Digital, ahcdm_02883_271-275)
      - Cinematic Photograph, Black & White, 1958 (Box 106)
      - Score, undated (Box 33)
    - The Man from U.N.C.L.E. Movie: "One of Our Spies is Missing"
      - Score, 1966 (Box 33)
    - One Potato, Two Potato
      - Booth Sheets, undated (Box 36)
      - Cassette: Screen Archives - Gerald Fried "One Potato, Two Potato", October 11, 1994 (Box 99)
      - Poster, undated (Box 106)
      - Promotional Cinematic Photographs, undated (Box 105)
      - Score, 1 of 2, undated (Box 36)
      - Score, 2 of 2, undated (Box 36)
    - Psyche Ascending
      - Score, 2013 (Box 36)
    - The Restless Breed
      - Score, undated (Box 35)
    - The Return of Dracula
      - Cinematic Photographs, Color, 1958 (Box 106)
    - The Second Time Around
      - Cassette: Screen archives - Gerald Fried "2nd Time Around", October 27, 1994 (Box 99)
      - CD: Tapes 1-3, 1961 (Digital, ahcdm_02883_178-179)
    - Stanley Kubrick's The Day of the Fight
      - CD: Kubrick music #2, undated (Digital, ahcdm_02883_339)
      - CDs, 1951 (Digital, ahcdm_02883_331)
      - Orchestra Parts, undated (Box 35)
      - Score, undated (Box 35)
      - Score, undated (Box 35)
    - Stanley Kubrick's Fear and Desire
      - Backup Parts, undated (Box 37)
      - CD: Master, 1953 (Digital, ahcdm_02883_341)
      - CDs: Proto, Master, Straight Transfer, 1953 (Digital, ahcdm_02883_420-425)
      - Movie Stills, undated (Box 35)
      - Part II, Orchestra Score, undated (Box 37)
      - Reel-to-Reel: WYNC, 1951 (Box 99)
      - Score, "A Grave for Others", undated (Box 37)
      - Score, Parts I and II, undated (Box 35)
    - Stanley Kubrick's Killer's Kiss
      - CDs: "The Killing" and "Killer's Kiss", 1955-1968 (Digital, ahcdm_02883_321-324)
      - Score and Cue Sheet, undated (Box 37)
      - Score and Parts, undated (Box 38)
    - Stanley Kubrick's The Killing
      - CDs: Proto, Primitive, Master, 1956 (Digital, ahcdm_02883_108-110)
      - Cinematic Photographs, Black & White and Color, 1956 (Box 106)
      - Full Score, undated (Box 38)
      - Orchestra Parts, undated (Box 38)
      - Score and Backup Parts, undated (Box 39)
      - Score (CD Version?), undated (Box 39)
      - Score, "Bed of Fear", undated (Box 39)
    - Stanley Kubrick's Paths of Glory
      - "The Patrol",Parts and Original Score, undated (Box 39)
      - Score, undated (Box 41)
    - Survive!
      - 3 Reel-to-Reels and CDs: Masters with Slates, 1976 (Box 101 and Digital, ahcdm_02883_053-056)
      - Correspondence and Breakdown of Costs for Recording Session, May 17, 1976-June 2, 1976 (Box 41)
      - Score, 1 of 2, undated (Box 41)
      - Score, 2 of 2, undated (Box 41)
    - Terror in a Texas Town
      - Cinematic Photographs, Color, undated (Box 106)
      - Score, undated (Box 97)
    - Timbuktu
      - CDs: Slates, Proto, Sequenced, Sequenced with Slates, 1959 (Digital, ahcdm_02883_342-346)
      - Cinematic Photograph, Color, undated (Box 106)
      - Score, undated (Box 41)
    - Too Late the Hero
      - Cassette, 1970 (Box 100)
      - Cassette: Gerald Fried, 1970 (Box 99)
      - Cassettes: 52nd Street Tape Duplication of Reels 1-7, 1970 (Box 100)
      - DAT Cassettes, 1970 (Digital, ahcdm_02883_402-408)
      - Score, 1 of 4, undated (Box 40)
      - Score, 2 of 4, undated (Box 40)
      - Score, 3 of 4, undated (Box 40)
      - Score, 4 of 4, undated (Box 40)
    - Trooper Hook
      - Cinematic Photograph, Color, undated (Box 106)
      - Score, 1 of 2, undated (Box 109)
      - Score, 2 of 2, undated (Box 109)
    - Twenty Plus Two
      - 2 Reel-to-Reels and CD: Reels 1-2, undated (Box 98 and Digital, ahcdm_02883_035)
      - CDs(Commercial): Gerald Fried - The Private Issue Collection", 1961 (Box 98 and Digital, ahcdm_02883_041)
      - Score, 1 of 2, undated (Box 42)
      - Score, 2 of 2, undated (Box 42)
    - The Vampire
      - Cinematic Photograph, Color, 1957 (Box 106)
    - Vigilante Force
      - 2 Reel-to-Reels and CDs: Reels 1-2 - Master, Proto, Short Version, Master with Slates, 1976 (Box 103 and Digital, ahcdm_02883_247-251)
      - Score, 1975 (Box 42)
    - What Ever Happened to Aunt Alice?
      - 3 Reel-to-Reels, 1969 (Box 103)
      - CDs: Demos, Masters with Slates, "The Killing of Sister George", 1968-1969 (Digital, ahcdm_02883_064-069)
      - Score, 1 of 2, 1969 (Box 42)
      - Score, 2 of 2, 1969 (Box 42)
      - String Quartet Score, undated (Box 43)
    - The Young Lions (Sketch)
      - Score, undated (Box 43)
  - Sub-series 6. TV Series & TV Movies
    - The 2-5
      - Score for Pilot, 1978 (Box 43)
    - The Beasts Are on the Streets
      - Cassette: "Beast Mix", 1978 (Box 103)
      - Cassettes: #1-3, 1978 (Box 103)
      - CDs: Reels 1-4 - Masters, Proto, with Slates, 1978 (Digital, ahcdm_02883_170-173)
      - Score, 1 of 2, 1978 (Box 44)
      - Score, 2 of 2, 1978 (Box 44)
    - Ben Casey
      - Score, undated (Box 45)
    - Breaking Point
      - CDs: "Breaking Point #3" Sequenced Master, Isolated Proto, with Slates, 1963 (Digital, ahcdm_02883_262-264)
      - Reel to Reel, 1963 (Box 98)
      - Score, "Fire & Ice Episode, undated (Box 45)
    - Breaking Up Is Hard to Do
      - Cassette:Music by Gerry Fried, 1979 (Box 99)
      - Score, undated (Box 45)
    - Casablanca
      - 773 - Discs 1-2, 774 - Discs 1-2, 1983 (Digital, ahcdm_02883_256-261)
      - Cassettes: Production #167770 and #167773, 1982-1983 (Box 100)
      - CD: #1, 1983 (Digital, ahcdm_02883_014)
      - Score, "Divorce Casablanca Style" Episode, 1982 (Box 46)
      - Score, "Jenny" Episode, undated (Box 46)
    - The Chisholms
      - Score, undated (Box 47)
    - Condominium
      - CDs: Parts 1-2, Master with Slates, 1980 (Digital, ahcdm_02883_228-233)
      - Score, Episode 1, 1980 (Box 47)
      - Score, Episode 2, 1 of 2, 1980 (Box 48)
      - Score, Episode 2, 2 of 2, 1980 (Box 48)
    - Cruise into Terror (Voyage into Evil)
      - Cassettes: Cruise, "Voyage into Evil" - Spelling Goldberg, 1978 (Box 103)
      - CDs: From Cassettes 1 and 3, First Mock-up, Back-up, 1978 (Digital, ahcdm_02883_374-376)
      - Score, 1 of 2, January 22, 1978 (Box 49)
      - Score, 1 of 2, January 22, 1978 (Box 49)
    - Deputy Seraph
      - Scores, Epilogue and Prologue, undateds (Box 50)
    - Dino
      - CD: Sal Mineo vocal, 1957 (Digital, ahcdm_02883_197-198)
      - Phono Disc: Soundtrack, 1957 (Box 104)
      - Reel-to-Reel: Vocal, undated (Box 99)
      - Score, 1 of 2, undated (Box 50)
      - Score, 1 of 2, undated (Box 50)
    - Disaster on the Coastliner
      - CDs: Master with Slates, Isolated Cue Master, 1979 (Digital, ahcdm_02883_296-298)
      - Score, 1 of 2, undated (Box 49)
      - Score, 2 of 2, undated (Box 49)
    - Drop-Out Mother
      - CDs: Masters, 1988 (Digital, ahcdm_02883_166-169)
      - Score and Orchestra Chart, 1987 (Box 51)
    - Dundee and Culhane
      - Score, Prod.9, "The Murderer Stallion Brief", undated (Box 52)
    - Dynasty
      - Cassettes: Episodes 76 and 79, 1984 (Box 100)
      - CDs: #76 and #79 with Slates, 1981-1989 (Digital, ahcdm_02883_132-137)
      - Score, "The Accident" Episode, undated (Box 51)
      - Score, "The Proposal" Episode, 1984 (Box 52)
    - Embassy
      - 4 Reel-to-Reels and CDs: Masters with Slates, 1985 (Box 101 and Digital, ahcdm_02883_072-074)
      - Score, 1 of 2, 1985 (Box 52)
      - Score, 2 of 2, 1985 (Box 52)
    - Emergency!
      - Score, "The Convention" Episode, undated (Box 53)
      - Score, "The Greatest Rescues of Emergency!" Episode, 1 of 2, undated (Box 53)
      - Score, "The Greatest Rescues of Emergency!" Episode 2 of 2, undated (Box 53)
    - Flamingo Road
      - Cassette: Production #189127, 1978 (Box 103)
      - CD: Isolated Proto, Slated Master, Production #189127, "The Jealous Wife", 1980-1981 (Digital, ahcdm_02883_189-193)
      - Music Cue Sheet Summaries, 1981 (Box 54)
      - Score, Episode 1, undated (Box 54)
      - Score for Pilot, 1980 (Box 53)
    - For Us the Living: The Medgar Evers Story
      - CDs: Master with Slates, Without Slates, 1983 (Digital, ahcdm_02883_240-242)
      - Score, undated (Box 54)
    - Francis Gary Powers: The True Story of the U-2 Spy Incident
      - Score, Bass Sheets, undated (Box 55)
      - Score, Percussion Sheets, undated (Box 55)
    - Gauguin the Savage
      - CD, 1980 (Digital, ahcdm_02883_045)
      - Score, 1 of 2, undated (Box 56)
      - Score, 2 of 2, undated (Box 56)
    - Gilligan's Island
      - CD and 3 Reel-to-Reels: "The Harlem Globetrotters on Gilligan's Island", Reels 1,2, and 3, 1981 (Box 98 and Digital, ahcdm_02883_019)
      - CDs: "Castaways on Gilligan's Island", "Gilligan's Song", Isolated Master, Master with Slates, 1979 (Digital, ahcdm_02883_285-289)
      - CDs: "The Harlem Globetrotters on Gilligan's Island",Isoltaed Cue Master, Proto,Master with Slates, undated (Digital, ahcdm_02883_293-294)
      - Miscellaneous Scores, 1965-1966 (Box 58)
      - Music Timing, "The Harlem Globetrotters on Gilligan's Island" Episode, April 14, 1981-May 5, 1981 (Box 58)
      - Reels: "Rescue from Gilligan's Island" Master, Reels 1-3, 1978 (Digital, ahcdm_02883_451-453)
      - Score, "The Castaways on Gilligan's Island" Episode, 1979-1981 (Box 57)
      - Score, "Gilligan Meets Jungle Boy Episode, 1964-1965 (Box 57)
      - Score, "The Harlem Globetrotters on Gilligan's Island" Episode, 1 of 2, undated (Box 57)
      - Score, "The Harlem Globetrotters on Gilligan's Island" Episode, 2 of 2, undated (Box 57)
      - Score, " How to Be a Hero" Episode, January, 1965 (Box 58)
      - Score, "Rescue from Gilligan's Island" Episode, 1 of 2, September 20, 1978 (Box 58)
      - Score, "Rescue from Gilligan's Island" Episode, 2 of 2, September 20, 1978 (Box 58)
      - Score,"So Sorry, My Island Now" Episode, December 23, 1964 (Box 59)
    - The Girl from U.N.C.L.E.
      - Score, "The Drublegratz Affair" Episode, undated (Box 59)
    - Gunsmoke
      - Score, "Dry Road to Nowhere" Episode, March, 1965 (Box 59)
    - I Will Fight No More, Forever
      - CDs and 3 Reel-to-Reels: parts 1-2, 1975 (Box 103 and Digital, ahcdm_02883_222, 310-312)
      - Score, 1 of 2, 1975 (Box 59)
      - Score, 2 of 2, 1975 (Box 59)
    - The Immigrants
      - Film Composer Collector Cards, 1978 (Box 105)
      - Score, Production #51601, 1978 (Box 60)
      - Score, Production #51602, 1978 (Box 60)
    - The Incredible Journey of Doctor Meg Laurel
      - CDs and DVD: Discs 1-3, Parts 1-2, 1979 (Digital, ahcdm_02883_371-373)
      - Score, 1 of 2, undated (Box 61)
      - Score, 2 of 2, undated (Box 61)
    - It's About Time
      - CDs: With Slates, undated (Digital, ahcdm_02883_046-048)
      - Score, 1966 (Box 61)
    - Jericho
      - Score, Conductor Sheets, October 10, 1966 (Box 61)
    - Johnny Midnight
      - Score,"X Equals Murder" Episode, undated (Box 61)
    - A Killer in the Family
      - CD: Reel 1, 1979-1983 (Digital, ahcdm_02883_018)
      - CDs: Master with Slates, 1983 (Digital, ahcdm_02883_057-059)
      - Score, 1983 (Box 62)
    - M-Squad
      - Score, Production #, undated (Box 62)
    - Man Eaters are Loose!
      - Score, April, 1978 (Box 62)
    - The Man from U.N.C.L.E.
      - Episodes 7458-8467 (13 Cassette Tapes, 13 CDs), 1964-1968
        - Alexander the Greater I and II
          - Cassette: Episodes 7458-7459 (Box 98 and Digital, ahcdm_02883_020-032)
          - CDs: Isolated, Master, 1965 (Digital, ahcdm_02883_368-370)
          - Score, Booth Sheets, Parts I and II, 1965 (Box 63)
          - Score, Part I, 1965 (Box 63)
        - Apple a Day
          - Cassette: Episode 8453 (Box 98 and Digital, ahcdm_02883_020-032)
          - Score, Conductor Sheets, 1967 (Box 63)
        - Arabian
          - Cassette: Episode 7484 (Box 98 and Digital, ahcdm_02883_020-032)
          - Score, Booth Sheets, 1965 (Box 63)
        - Bat Cave
          - Cassette: Episode 8418 (Box 98 and Digital, ahcdm_02883_020-032)
          - Score, 1966 (Box 64)
        - The Casbah Affair
          - Score, Conductor Sheets, 1966 (Box 64)
        - Cherry Blossom
          - Cassette: Episode 7487 (Box 98 and Digital, ahcdm_02883_020-032)
          - Score, 1965 (Box 64)
        - Come with Me to the Casbah
          - Cassette: Episode 8436 (Box 98 and Digital, ahcdm_02883_020-032)
        - Deadly Goddess
          - Cassette: Episode 8412 (Box 98 and Digital, ahcdm_02883_020-032)
          - Score, 1965 (Box 64)
        - Deadly Quest
          - Cassette: Episode 8467 (Box 98 and Digital, ahcdm_02883_020-032)
          - Score, 1967 (Box 64)
        - Discotheque
          - Cassette: Episode 7476 (Box 98 and Digital, ahcdm_02883_020-032)
          - Score, undated (Box 64)
        - Dreadful Affair
          - Score, Conductor Sheets, 1966 (Box 65)
          - Score, undated (Box 64)
        - Foreign Legion
          - Cassette: Episode 8415 (Box 98 and Digital, ahcdm_02883_020-032)
          - Score, 1966 (Box 65)
        - Gorilla Affair
          - Score, undated (Box 65)
          - Score, 1966 (Box 65)
        - Her Master's Voice
          - Cassette: Episode 8426 (Box 98 and Digital, ahcdm_02883_020-032)
          - Score, 1966 (Box 65)
        - Hot Number
          - Cassette: Episode 8456 (Box 98 and Digital, ahcdm_02883_020-032)
          - Score, Conductor Sheets, 1967 (Box 65)
        - Indian Affairs
          - Cassette: Episode 7492 (Box 98 and Digital, ahcdm_02883_020-032)
        - Italian Affair
          - Cassette: Episode 8438 (Box 98 and Digital, ahcdm_02883_020-032)
        - It's All Greek to Me
          - Cassette: Episode 8445-8446 (Box 98 and Digital, ahcdm_02883_020-032)
          - Score, 1967 (Box 66)
        - Jingle Bells
          - Cassette: Episode 8443 (Box 98 and Digital, ahcdm_02883_020-032)
          - Score, Conductor Sheets, 1966 (Box 66)
        - Monks of St. Thomas
          - Cassette: Episode 8429 (Box 98 and Digital, ahcdm_02883_020-032)
          - Score, 1966 (Box 66)
        - Moonglow Affair
          - Cassette: Episode 7490 (Box 98 and Digital, ahcdm_02883_020-032)
          - Score, Conductor Sheets, 1966 (Box 66)
        - My Friend the Gorilla
          - Cassette: Episodes 8440 and 8450 (Box 98 and Digital, ahcdm_02883_020-032)
        - Napoleon's Tomb
          - Cassette: Episode 8431 (Box 98 and Digital, ahcdm_02883_020-032)
          - Score, Conductor Sheets, 1967 (Box 66)
        - Not so Far Safari Affair
          - Score, Conductor Sheets, 1966 (Box 66)
        - Off broadway
          - CDs: Master, Discs 1-2, Isolated, undated (Digital, ahcdm_02883_364-367)
          - Cassette: Episode 8427 (Box 98 and Digital, ahcdm_02883_020-032)
          - Score, Conductor Sheets, 1966 (Box 66)
        - Return of the Man from U.N.C.L.E.
          - Cassettes: Masters, 1964-1968 (Box 100)
          - Cassettes, 1983 (Box 99)
          - Score, 1 of 2, undated (Box 67)
          - Score, 2 of 2, undated (Box 67)
        - Sort of Do-It-Yourself Dreadful
          - Cassette: Episode 8413 (Box 98 and Digital, ahcdm_02883_020-032)
        - Super-Colossal
          - Cassette: Episode 8437 (Box 98 and Digital, ahcdm_02883_020-032)
          - Score, Conductor Sheets, 1966 (Box 67)
        - Test Tube Killer
          - Cassette: Episode 8468 (Box 98 and Digital, ahcdm_02883_020-032)
          - Score, Conductor Sheets, 1967 (Box 67)
        - Very Important Zombie
          - Cassette: Episode 8404 (Box 98 and Digital, ahcdm_02883_020-032)
          - Score, 1965 (Box 68)
      - Mixed Episode Titles
        - "Arabian" and "Do it Yourself Dreadful" U.N.C.L.E. Master, Isolated Proto, Discs 1-2 (CDs), 1965 (Digital, ahcdm_02883_347-350)
        - "Hot Number" and "An Apple a Day" Suites, Isolate (CDs), 1967 (Digital, ahcdm_02883_351-354)
        - "Monks of St. Thomas" and "Discoteque" U.N.C.L.E. Master, Discs 1-2, Isolated Proto, "Test tube Killer", "Jingle Bells" (CDs), 1965-1967 (Digital, ahcdm_02883_355-363)
    - Mannix
      - Score and Orchestra Chart, October 1, 1969, undated (Box 68)
    - Medical Story
      - CDs: Production #183406, 1975 (Box 98 and Digital, ahcdm_02883_009-011)
      - Reel-to-Reel, undated (Box 103)
    - Mission Impossible
      - Score (Bound), undated (Box 69)
      - Score, "The Code" Episode, undated (Box 68)
      - Score, "The Diplomat" Episode, undated (Box 68)
    - Mr. Terrific
      - Score, "The Formula is Stolen" Episode, undated (Box 70)
      - Score, "Matchless" Episode, undated (Box 69)
      - Score, Unknown Episode, undated (Box 70)
    - Moviola
      - CDs:, 1980 (Digital, ahcdm_02883_103-107)
      - Score, "The Silent Lovers" Episode, undated (Box 70)
    - Murder Is Easy
      - CDs: Masters with Slates, 1982 (Digital, ahcdm_02883_060-063)
      - CDs: Sequenced, Back-up, 1982 (Digital, ahcdm_02883_290-291)
      - Score, undated (Box 70)
    - My Three Sons
      - Reel to Reel, 1967 (Box 98)
      - Score, Unknown Episode, undated (Box 70)
      - Score, Unknown Episode, undated (Box 70)
    - The Mystic Warrior
      - Reviews, etc., 1984 (Box 70)
      - Score and Program, 1 of 3, 2003, undated (Box 71)
      - Score and Program, 2 of 3, 2003, undated (Box 71)
      - Score and Program, 3 of 3, 2003, undated (Box 72)
      - Score, Unknown Episode, undated (Box 70)
    - Napoleon and Josephine: A Love Story
      - Cassettes, 1987 (Box 100)
      - CDs: Parts 2-3, Suite, 1987 (Digital, ahcdm_02883_454-463)
      - Reel-to-Reel, 1987 (Box 103)
      - Score, Part I, 1 of 2, undated (Box 72)
      - Score, Part I, 2 of 2, undated (Box 72)
      - Score, Part II, 1 of 2, undated (Box 72)
      - Score, Part II, 2 of 2, undated (Box 72)
      - Score, Part III, 1 of 2, undated (Box 73)
      - Score, Part III, 2 of 2, undated (Box 73)
    - Number 96
      - Reel-to-Reel and CD: Roll 1-2 - Master with Slates, 1980 (Box 102 and Digital, ahcdm_02883_131)
      - Score, Unknown Episode, undated (Box 73)
    - Off to See the Wizard
      - Score, Conductor Sheets, July, 1966 (Box 73)
    - The Ordeal of Dr. Mudd
      - CDs: Reels 1-3 - Masters with Slates, Mock-up, 1980 (Digital, ahcdm_02883_161-165)
      - Score, 1 of 2, undated (Box 73)
      - Score, 2 of 2, undated (Box 73)
    - Police Story
      - CDs and Reel-to-Reel: Production #183572, 1975 (Box 98 and Digital, ahcdm_02883_007-008 and 011)
    - Police Woman
      - CDs and Reel-to-Reels: Production #183847 and #183853, 1975 (Box 98 and Digital, ahcdm_02883_001-006)
      - Score, "The Buttercup Killer" Episode, undated (Box 74)
      - Score, "The Yound and the Fair" Episode, undated (Box 74)
    - Rawhide
      - Score, "Moment in the Sun" Episode, January 12, 1965 (Box 74)
      - Score, "The Winter Soldier" Episode, February 22, 1965 (Box 74)
    - The Rebels
      - CDs: Parts 1-2 - Master, with Slates, Proto, Unsequenced Proto, 1979 (Digital, ahcdm_02883_428-443)
      - Reel to Reel, undated (Box 99)
      - Score, Production #52101, 1 of 2, 1979 (Box 75)
      - Score, Production #52101, 2 of 2, 1979 (Box 75)
      - Score, Production #52102, 1979 (Box 75)
    - Rip-Cord
      - Score, undated (Box 75)
    - Riverboat
      - Reel-to-Reel, undated (Box 103)
      - Score, "The Blowup" Episode, undated (Box 76)
      - Score, "Chicota Landing" Episode, undated (Box 76)
      - Score, "Devil in Skirts" Episode, undated (Box 76)
      - Score, "End of a Dream" Episode, undated (Box 76)
      - Score, "Fort Epitaph" Episode, undated (Box 76)
      - Score, Production #12357, undated (Box 77)
      - Score, "The Quota" Episode, Production #12355, undated (Box 77)
      - Score, "River Champion" Episode, Production #12354 (Box 77)
      - Score, "That Taylor Affair" Episode, Production #12359, undated (Box 77)
      - Score, "Trunk Full of Dreams" Episode, Production #12355, undated (Box 77)
      - Score, "The Two Faces of Grey Holden" Episode, Production #12352, undated (Box 78)
      - Score, "The Water of Gorgeous Springs" Episode, Production #12362, undated (Box 78)
      - Score, "The Wichita Arrows" Episode, Production #12336, undated (Box 78)
      - Score, "Witness No Evil" Episode, Production #12363, undated (Box 78)
      - Score, "Zigzag" Episode, Production #12366, undated (Box 78)
      - Scores, Miscellaneous, undated (Box 77)
      - Scores, Miscellaneous, undated (Box 77)
    - Road Block
      - CDs: Sequenced Master, Unidentified, with Slates Discs 1-2, Discs 1-3, Isolated Cue Master, undated (Digital, ahcdm_02883_377-384)
      - Score, undated (Box 79)
    - Roots I
      - Betamax Tapes: Parts 1-3, 5, and 7, 1977 (Box 100,102)
      - CD, Record, 6 Reel to Reels, Cassette Tape: Soundtrack and Demo, Reels 1-6, 1977 (Box 101 and Digital, ahcdm_02883_102)
      - CDs, 11 Reel to Reels, 9 DAT Cassettes: Reels 1-9, 1977 (Box 102 and Digital, ahcdm_02883_117-125)
      - Cue Sheets, 1976-1977 (Box 79)
      - Photographs from event, undated (Box 79)
      - Program, "Emmy Awards for Nighttime Programming", 1977 (Box 79)
      - Reel-to-Reel: 52nd Street Tape Duplication - "Roots" Soundtrack Cassette (Reels 1-5), 1977 (Box 99)
      - Reel-to-Reel: "African Songs", 1977 (Box 99)